Subtitle By: MARSH-MARIE
Stop right there.
Get on the floor now.
Ladies.
I wouldn't do that.
Who the fuck are you?
What do you want?
Lucy Swanson.
Lucy was here a week ago
on a night out
with her friends.
Thing is, this is
the last place she was seen.
Do you know how many bored little
rich girls run away from home?
Happens every day
in the big city.
Unfortunately,
your boys did a terrible job
of disposing of the evidence.
The police found
her body last night.
Lucy's parents
are friends of mine,
so here I am.
So here you are.
So what now, then?
Now, turn yourselves in
and confess.
And what happens
if we say fuck you?
- That.
- Kill this fucking...
Haven't lost your touch,
I see.
Frost, what are you
doing here?
Got something to tell you.
Nope.
Don't you want to
know how I found you?
Satellites, cameras,
etcetera?
John, look,
I needed to speak
to you face to face.
About a job.
How many times?
Not. Interested.
You will be this time.
It's Teague.
Sean Teague is dead.
This was taken yesterday.
The operative who sent it was deep
undercover for the past two years.
He was about to take his targets down
when he was introduced to an arms dealer
that turned out to be Teague.
I'm putting a team together to catch
Teague, and I want you to lead it.
You want me to bring
Teague in... alive?
I know what he did to you and your
team, but we need Teague breathing.
His intel and contacts alone
are enough to bring down
the baddest of the bad.
Come on,
do it for your country.
Oh, that's rich
coming from you.
Okay, do it
for yourself, then.
Meaning?
Meaning you bring
Teague in, in one piece,
the department wipes
your slate clean.
All is forgiven.
No more running.
Think about it, John.
Bring Teague in alive,
and you get
your life back again.
Gentlemen. Ladies.
You all know
Commander Grayson.
- Morning, everyone.
- Morning.
Our target.
Sean Teague.
As you all know,
Teague was an elite operative,
one of our best,
until he turned on his team
during their final mission
in Eastern Europe
several years ago.
Many of them
met with rather...
grisly ends.
Quite.
After going rogue,
Teague was responsible
for the deaths
of dozens of personnel,
as well as countless civilians in
mercenary operations across the globe.
Arms deals,
smuggling state secrets,
assassinations.
You name it,
Teague profited from it.
Well, yeah he did.
Until he was reported killed
two years ago in the D.R.C.
Yes, well, we've
all heard that story.
Authorities on the ground confirmed
that Teague had been killed,
but he's here now,
and we're going to bring him in.
Who's the tree trunk?
You're kidding.
It's only John fucking Gold.
- Get away.
- Uh-huh.
Wonder how many people
he's killed this week.
Five.
So far.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Lynch and Shapiro,
you've somewhat preempted me.
Everybody, meet John Gold.
Nobody knows Teague
better than Gold,
especially in the field.
And nobody has a more compelling
reason to bring him in.
From what I've heard,
you'll more likely put
a bullet behind Teague's ear
than put him behind bars.
People do like to talk,
don't they?
Your mission is
breach Teague's location,
transport him to
an off-the-books airbase,
then fly him
to an ever-so-hush-hush
black site secure facility,
where he'll live out
his days in a steel box.
So what's the play, boss?
Gold here will lead,
with you two reprobates
providing ground support
and flying-slash-
driving services.
Shit work. Standard.
That's what
we get paid for.
What?
They pay you for this?
That's enough, you two.
Kelso, Plachecki and Stiles,
you'll serve and support
the operation from here.
Any questions?
Course not.
I'll see you at the R.V.
I'm sorry we can't give you the
support you need for this one, John.
You know I can't be seen
to authorize a full team.
If news about Teague
being alive got out,
top brass will have
a major flap-on.
But Lynch and Shapiro
are two of the best.
Believe it or not.
A team can be a liability.
Teague taught me that.
Morning, lads.
- Boss.
Nice morning for it.
- Heard from Pearl yet?
- Not yet.
We agreed on radio silence
until she arrives.
Yeah, yeah,
just in case.
Pretty smart...
coming from you.
Okay, lads,
we're here for the duration
until we hear from Pearl.
- Smoke them if you've got them.
- Come on.
What's all this?
What?
Oh, uh, nothing.
What is all this?
I, uh...
I... I really need a piss.
So go take a piss.
What am I, your mother?
Ahhh...
Better than sex!
Then you're doing it wrong.
Fuck!
Steady!
As I live and breathe.
John Gold.
Teague.
You're coming with me.
Yeah, of course I am.
Lads!
Bennett, move!
Go.
Go, go, go.
Teague!
Hands in the air!
Don't stop us now.
We're just starting to have some fun.
Assume the position.
Or what?
To be continued.
Are you sure you're
going to make our window?
We've got a tight timeframe
to get that plane in the air.
Yeah, we'll make it.
Our E.T.A's
about 60 minutes.
Okay, great. Just get Teague to that
airbase, and we can all breathe out.
Yep, copy that.
Lynch and Shapiro
are securing Teague,
and we'll be on our way
in a few.
Just make sure that plane
is good to go.
Twat's ready for transport.
Hey, you're going
nowhere, mate.
Here's Prince Charming now.
I'll keep you updated.
Stay frosty.
Yeah, funny,
I've never heard that before.
This is excellent,
by the way.
I know.
Good to go.
Believe it or not, Teague,
this is all for your own good.
You're being flown to a remote,
black site prison
'cause there's too many people out
here that want your head on a pike.
People like you?
You're a traitor,
you're a murderer,
and you sacrificed our own team.
Now, you either pay
for those crimes this way,
or someone's going
to tear you limb from limb.
Alleged crimes.
And I'm supposed to believe
all this from a man
who wants to see me
dead more than most?
For my own good, eh?
That's bullshit.
Let's go.
Get in! Get in!
I knew it... you're
trying to kill me!
Don't be ridiculous,
we'd just let him do it.
Anyone got eyes on the shooter?
Right, we need a volunteer
to draw their fire.
Fuck off.
- Fucking...!
- Where are they?
Three o'clock, tower.
Probably one of Teague's...
- No, Teague's the target.
- Bollocks.
Whoa...
- Maybe.
- Let's go.
On it.
- Mine.
- Really?
Lynch! Step on it.
Hold onto
your balls back there.
Talk to me.
We had an unexpected guest,
but we're on our way.
Any idea who it was?
Not a clue, but they
wanted Teague's head.
And nearly got it.
I'll keep you posted.
We're on our way, people.
Take it steady.
Hey, hope you've got some
nice hot stewardesses
on this flight for me, John.
I wouldn't get
your hopes up, Teague.
You're going to prison,
not Ibiza.
And they're called
cabin crew these days.
Touch a nerve there, did I?
Oh, for...
We've got incoming.
Shit!
Lynch, floor it!
Come on, then.
Shit.
Dead end!
Brace! Brace!
Move! Now!
Everyone all right?
Fuck off.
Lynch, you okay?
Yeah, just great.
Look, I don't give a shit
about whoever's out there,
but you either give me a gun or
you get me the fuck out of here.
Someone's finally
got to the big,
bad tough-as-fuck
Sean Teague.
I'll shake them
by the hand.
Gold.
Check this out.
You think we can make it
over to that factory?
Yeah,
that'll do for now.
I'll draw his fire,
you two follow Lynch.
I'll catch up to you once
I've dealt with our new friend.
Or we could just hand
Teague over to whoever that is.
You're supposed
to protect me.
Tell me again
what my job is?
Shapiro.
You see, John?
That's what it
comes down to.
Me, and a quarter-ounce
of lead.
Don't tempt me.
Guys, if we're going,
we should go now.
Right, then.
Move!
Who the fuck are you?
Greetings.
Now this...
This is gonna be fun.
How are we doing?
We got held up again.
Our new friend
took out our van.
There's something else.
We were attacked
by another team.
As in a different team
that attacked both of you?
That is what the sentence
that I just said
would mean, yes.
Any idea who they were?
I didn't hang around
to find out.
I'm regrouping
with the others now.
Okay.
We're not authorized,
but fuck this sitting
on our thumbs shit.
I'm going in there
to help our guys.
Fancy it?
Just say the word.
That's what I Like to hear.
Let's get going, people.
How long should we give it?
Ten minutes?
I mean we can't wait
much longer than...
Who was that back there?
Didn't get a name.
They're still out there.
Some others too.
Others like who?
No idea.
You?
How the fuck do I know?
So it could be anyone, then.
Right, we need
to get to that airbase.
Take a look around,
see if we can find some wheels.
You lot don't know what
you've got yourselves into.
Quiet!
Move!
Gold.
Gold!
That's it, get up.
Say hello to my boys,
and my beautiful fiancée.
We're going to use this
to keep track of you.
How long does
it take to work?
Should already
be up and running.
We're good.
Just don't lose that phone.
I told you there'd be no plane for
me, didn't I?
You just wouldn't listen.
You're going nowhere, Teague.
It's Mr. Teague to you.
Cut these, Gunnar.
Keep them here.
Any trouble,
you kill the chick first.
Fuck you!
You got it, boss.
When you're all done
with the womanfolk,
why don't you just come show
us how tough you really are.
I'm gonna need this.
Moan feebly if that's okay.
Good. Right.
I'm gonna
go kill those guys,
while you go after Teague.
Right...
But don't engage him.
Just let me know
where you are.
Yeah, but hold on.
I...
Hey, Gold!
I always heard you were some
kind of one-man killing machine.
So, what're you waiting for?
Hang on, I'll be through in a
second to kick your teeth in.
Go find Teague,
and let me know where you are.
We'll get him together.
Okay.
Don't get killed and stuff.
You too.
Right, then.
You all right, mate?
Finally.
Pleasure to meet you,
Mr. Gold.
Likewise.
So...
you're John Gold.
The John Gold?
Yep.
You know, Teague told us
all these stories
about how bloodthirsty you are.
Yet here we all are with...
these.
And there you are with...
With that.
I mean, what're you
even going to do with...
- Kendrick, get the car.
- Okay.
Be out of here in five.
Knew you'd
come through, babe.
Teague!
Stay where you are.
Look, we've got
somewhere to go.
Why don't you
just back off?
What? This
shouldn't take long.
Yeah, you're right,
it'll take me about 30 seconds.
Maybe we should
offer her a job.
Fuck...
Shoot him!
Say goodbye, prick-hole.
Shit!
Stoppage.
Okay, okay.
Let's get bloody.
Get behind me.
Do something, then.
Just stay back.
Step aside.
This isn't your fight.
Who are you?
Who is she?
Long story,
but she should be dead.
Oh, your men
tried all right.
You're trying to save
the life of a murderer,
which makes you
naive at best,
but you're not my problem.
Just get out of my way,
I don't want to hurt you.
Then don't.
But I'm not moving.
We're taking Teague
to prison, to face justice.
This is justice!
Well, come on, do it!
Don't rush me!
I'm killing a hero here.
It's a big moment for me.
Any last words?
Prepare to be
deeply embarrassed.
He's a live one, all right!
But not for long.
Here it comes.
Well, stop dicking around
and kill him!
I'm trying...
Last chance. Walk away.
Okay.
I tried.
All right.
Getting paid overtime
for this, right?
Well, thanks for
all your help.
You okay?
Where's Lynch?
Right, I'll deal with that,
you go cover the entrance.
We don't need any more
unexpected guests.
Roger that.
Use this.
Stand back, babe.
Come on, babe!
Let's go.
If you...
Teague!
You want to have a go
hand-to-hand?
Yeah, I fancy my chances.
Hey.
Whoever you are.
I can see you've
got your reasons,
but let us bring Teague
in the right way.
You don't understand, he...
Dumb fucking luck!
You're amazing,
but give it up.
Get real!
Gold!
Lynch! Hold on!
You okay?
We had a disagreement.
That's her specialty.
Long time, no see Jen.
You know her?
Jen Quaid.
Served with her father.
Until Teague
ended all that.
Let me go, Gold.
I've got no
problem with you.
Not this time.
We're taking
Teague to prison.
Three square meals a day
and a roof over his head?
After everything he's done?
That's not nearly enough,
and you know it.
I'm amazed you haven't
killed him yourself.
He's come close.
This is bigger than what
Teague's done to either of us.
You've got clean hands,
is that it?
My dad told me
about every mission.
All the horrible,
fucked-up shit
you guys did together.
And that's my point.
Do you want
to end up like us?
We both know that's not the
path your dad wanted for you.
So don't make this
harder than it has to be.
He's off again.
What do you want me to do?
Call Frost.
Check on Shapiro.
Then catch up with me.
I'll catch you later.
Boss.
- Lynch?
- Yeah it's me.
- Go ahead.
- We caught up with the sniper.
Name's Jen Quaid.
Christ, really?
Gold and I worked
with her old man.
Yeah, that's right.
She's tied up on the upper
level of our current location,
- if you want to pick her up.
- Copy that.
I've got Gold after me,
and I've got Jen Quaid after me,
so come and pick me up now.
We've got your position.
Just keep moving,
and we'll come to you.
Gunnar, Price.
Let's get movin'.
It's okay, chum.
It's okay.
Even if you get Teague
to that prison cell,
how long do
you think he'll last?
That's not my problem.
My mission ends once
he's in that cell.
All the shit Teague
has on the government.
All those black bag,
disavowable jobs
he did with my Dad and Gold?
They just want him
in there so
they can make sure
he dies on their terms.
Well, seeing as you want
Teague dead so badly,
why don't you
let us bring him in,
and he'll get what
you think he deserves.
No!
I have to kill him myself.
Jen.
Do you really think
your dad would want you
to go through all this
emotional agony and violence,
just to murder this one man?
Yes.
Okay, that's not
crazy or anything.
See you around.
Preferably not.
You're coming with me.
I'm going nowhere with you.
We don't have time for this.
You're not listening to me.
Or do you want me
to beat it into you?
I said we don't have
time for this.
How many of your mates
did I have killed again?
They were good men.
And you sold them out
for cold, hard cash.
I didn't do it for the money,
and you know that!
Teague!
Just listen...
Just like old times.
Always did like giving the
orders, didn't you, John?
This is your last warning.
If it wasn't for me,
Jen Quaid would have killed you by now.
If it weren't for
you slowing me down,
I'd have killed her!
I put everything
on the line for this country,
and I get made the scapegoat
for mistakes made over my head.
Shit rolls downhill.
You know that.
Years of loyal service,
and I get thrown on
the scrapheap.
Well, that's no excuse
for betraying your own team.
You wouldn't understand
until it happened to you.
Why don't you
just admit it, John.
You're enjoying this.
That's it.
That's the Gold I remember.
Come on!
Lynch advised
that Quaid is on the upper level.
Be ready to move in.
Is this what you want?
Is this what
you fucking want?
Enough...
Are you fucking
happy now, Teague?
Gold!
Hey, John.
You're killing him.
I'll call the team
to pick us up.
No.
Let's just get to
the airbase ourselves.
The three of us will be
harder for Jen to track.
You really think Jen's
still gonna be a problem?
There's one thing you need
to know about Jen Quaid.
She's always going
to be a problem.
Hello, boys.
Frost.
You know the routine, Jen.
Down on the ground.
Hands behind your head.
All right?
I want a chat about hazard
pay, but apart from that...
I'm "A"-okay.
Jen, I had a lot
of respect for your old man.
But we have to treat
you as an active threat,
so just behave
and let us bring you in.
What're we doing?
She's just some chick.
She's not even strapped.
That "chick"
nearly killed us all.
Twice.
She's amazing.
Kelso.
Cuff her.
Take cover!
Let's find some wheels.
This is a wild goose chase.
I'm done,
I ain't going any further.
Fine.
You stay here then,
wait for Jen to catch up
and shoot you in the head.
You fucking arsehole.
Hold fire! Hold fire!
Jen!
This is your last chance!
Surrender!
Right now!
Check it out.
Be careful. She's much more
dangerous than she looks.
Okay, on me.
Foyer clear.
You two, clear
the upper floor.
We'll check this level.
R.V. back here.
Roger that.
Let's go.
Keep comms open.
You heard the boss,
don't get brave.
Understood.
Just some chick?
I didn't mean...
Someone talk to me.
What's going on?
You okay?
Kelso?
Stiles?
What about this one?
Yeah.
I can work with this.
Think you can get it running?
Please.
Gold?
Cheers.
Right, straight
to the airbase.
- Roger that.
- You hear that, Teague?
Very soon we'll be
flying the friendly skies.
We'll see about that.
How's that,
Gunnar babe?
You look quite lovely, miss.
Not far now.
Take the next left.
You got it.
Okay.
So she got one over on me.
Can one of you at least
give me something to wear?
Sure. Here.
Quaid deactivated
the vehicle tracking system.
She could be anywhere.
Smart move.
Come on, you lot.
Let's get moving.
We're making good time.
Not far now.
Yeah, as long as this rust
bucket makes it that far.
Jesus...!
Come on, we've got to move.
This way, Mr. Teague.
That's fucked it, innit?
Teague!
Let's go.
Sean!
Come on, let's go.
You okay?
I'm seeing three of you,
but other than that,
I'm good.
Right, I'm going
to go after them.
You R.V. with Frost,
and I'll see you
at the airbase.
On it.
Fucker don't know
when to quit.
I've got this.
Guard her with your life.
What's he doing?
He needs to see
this through, miss.
This fucking guy.
Go and finish him.
Sean!
Not her again.
Shit.
Who is that?
That's the daughter of a man
I killed a long time ago.
Gold.
Jen, listen...
I understand why
you want to kill Teague.
And trust me,
I want to put a bullet in him too.
But it's not gonna
bring back my men.
And it's not gonna
bring back your dad.
So, please, help me
to do this the right way.
Here.
Kill them both.
You got it.
You get Teague,
I'll get the other guy.
Not bad.
We've got
to make that plane.
Why the fuck would
I go anywhere with you?
Well, in case
you've forgotten,
that's Jen Quaid.
You know he's killed
his own men, right?
Really going to
take his money?
I'm a mercenary.
The clue is
in the job description.
A highly trained
killing machine
who's been following
you all day,
and so far everything you've
tried to do to stop her
has failed.
Now, are you sure
your guy's
got what it takes
to bring her down?
'Cause I've got
to be honest with you...
my money's on her.
Now, move it!
You know what?
I might just stick around
and see how this pans out.
You know,
I'm really starting
to enjoy this job.
Damn it, Jen.
I've got to say, fighting you
has been a bit
of a thrill for me.
Best part is,
you're next.
You did good,
by the way.
You've got some moves.
And you've got
fighting spirit.
But now it's time to say...
Come on, let's go.
Fucking prick.
Ah, fuck.
Sean! Go!
Price, Gunnar. Shoot them!
Go after Teague,
I'll cover you.
You really want to take
on this lot by yourself?
You would.
Go now, before we lose him!
Take cover!
Renner Gunnar, Price, move in.
What the hell!
Close in,
we'll surround her.
Right, then.
Fuck me. You're like herpes...
I can't get rid of you.
On. Now.
Move in.
Shit.
She's a tricky one all right.
Room for one more?
That your summer look
or something?
Don't want to talk about it.
But where are
your trousers, though?
What's the latest?
Teague's men grabbed him,
and Gold was...
Speak of the devil,
and he shall appear.
Gold, you're on speaker and I'm
with the gang, so no sexy talk.
Gold! Let me off
this fucking thing!
So you got him again, then.
Yup. I got some wheels too.
Cool, we'll be at the
airbase in about ten minutes.
Roger that.
I'll see you soon.
You heard the man,
let's go.
Fucking dead man, Gold,
do you hear me?
Fucking dead man.
You might want
to hold on tight.
It's gonna be a bumpy ride.
Well?
Did you get her?
- Enjoy the ride?
- You're a prick.
Any more trouble
out of you,
and I'll be carrying you
onto that plane.
And how much trouble do
you think I can get in?
Just move.
Your gun, please.
That's what I'm talking about.
Now the keys, please.
You know, you might be
the most polite mercenary
I've ever encountered.
That's very kind
of you to say.
And we're taking the plane.
We're flying out of here.
No, you're getting
on that plane,
and you're going to prison.
I've had enough of this
you-and-me bollocks.
Get on your knees.
Do as you're told.
You might want
to stand back, darling.
This is over.
Now.
Hey, Teague.
That was quite the entrance.
Dad always said
I was dramatic.
Shit.
Teague's guys are already here.
Stiles.
Take point.
Let's go get these bastards.
Okay, stay here,
you'll be safe.
Do what you've got to do.
Move in.
I'm nearly out.
You?
Don't ask.
Go!
Fuck.
Believe it or not,
this is how I killed your old man!
Let's just go!
No I can't,
I've got to stay.
- No.
- I've got to finish this.
John!
You're really starting
to fucking irritate me now.
In my office.
Just... kill him...
already!
Ladies.
Do you really think
you can take me?
Fuck...
It's your choice.
Jen...
I've been there.
What're we going
to do with him now?
This ain't over, John.
Believe me,
this ain't over.
I'm coming
for your friends, John!
I'm coming for your kids,
John!
I'm coming for your dog!
Well, it may not be a plane,
but he's on his way.
Well done.
We'll debrief tomorrow
at 0900.
Did we win
this one, then?
Beers are on me,
so I guess.
Victory. Yay.
I'll see you in the pub.
You know Teague's probably
gonna die in that prison.
Maybe.
But I can live
with him being behind bars.
Think I can too.
Or I could just break in and
kill him if I change my mind.
So.
So?
How's it feel
to be a free man again?
S'all right.
Come on,
let's get plastered.
Hey, Gold!
Not far now.
Take the next left.
Hey, Gold!
You've got some moves.
Now this...
this is gonna be fun.
Finally.
What are you waiting for?
It's a big moment for me.
I'm a mercenary.
The clue
is in the job description.
We've got your position.
Just keep moving.
Here it comes.
Let's go.
Hey, Gold!
I've got to say,
fighting you
has been a bit of
a thrill for me.
Hey, Gold!
Not bad.
Subtitle By: MARSH-MARIE